--- InMemoryRunner.run Signature ---
(self, *, user_id: 'str', session_id: 'str', new_message: 'types.Content', run_config: 'Optional[RunConfig]' = None) -> 'Generator[Event, None, None]'

--- InMemoryRunner.run Docstring ---
Runs the agent.

NOTE:
  This sync interface is only for local testing and convenience purpose.
  Consider using `run_async` for production usage.

If event compaction is enabled in the App configuration, it will be
performed after all agent events for the current invocation have been
yielded. The generator will only finish iterating after event
compaction is complete.

Args:
  user_id: The user ID of the session.
  session_id: The session ID of the session.
  new_message: A new message to append to the session.
  run_config: The run config for the agent.

Yields:
  The events generated by the agent.

